whatiwear.com 2013-05-03

# PRIVACY | WhatIWear.com

WhatIWear.com (hereafter "WhatIWear") has developed this Privacy Policy ("Policy") in a continued effort to protect the privacy of our users. This Policy applies to your use of our website and any related services (the "Website") under the domain WhatIWear.com. By using or visiting the Website you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Website.

  * Like most website operators, WhatIWear collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. WhatIWear’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how WhatIWear’s visitors use its website. From time to time, WhatIWear may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. WhatIWear also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. WhatIWear only discloses user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

  * Certain visitors to WhatIWear’s websites choose to interact with WhatIWear in ways that require WhatIWear to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that WhatIWear gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at WhatIWear to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with WhatIWear – by purchasing items from WhatIWear, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, WhatIWear collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with WhatIWear. WhatIWear does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

  * WhatIWear may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. WhatIWear may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, WhatIWear does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

  * WhatIWear discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, affiliated companies and organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on WhatIWear’s behalf or to provide services available at WhatIWear’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, affiliated companies and organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using WhatIWear’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. WhatIWear will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, WhatIWear discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when WhatIWear believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of WhatIWear, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of WhatIWear and have supplied your email address, WhatIWear may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with WhatIWear and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. WhatIWear takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

  * A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. WhatIWear uses cookies to help WhatIWear identify and track visitors, their usage of WhatIWear website, and their website access preferences. WhatIWear visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using WhatIWear’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of WhatIWear’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

  * If WhatIWear, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that WhatIWear goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of WhatIWear may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

  * Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by WhatIWear and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

  * Although most changes are likely to be minor, WhatIWear may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in WhatIWear’s sole discretion. WhatIWear encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

  * PEOPLE SEARCH
    * __   Location
    * __   Gender
  * LOOK SEARCH
    * __   Category
    * __   Brand
    * __   Color
  * TREND SEARCH
    * __   Season
    * __   Year

KEYWORD/

LOCATION/

GENDER/

CATEGORY/

BRAND/

COLOR/

SEASON/

RELATION/

YEAR/

SEARCH
